{"test_questions": [[{"question": "An AutoCAD term that refers to a pre-drawn object which is stored in a drawing file and can be inserted into any other drawing file as needed is a ________.", "opta": "Block", "optb": "brick", "optc": "balloon", "optd": "none of the above", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Most architectural firms and mechanical design companies utilize different categories of blocks. These sets of blocks are usually housed in ________.", "opta": "block vaults", "optb": "block libraries", "optc": "block books", "optd": "block references", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In some circumstances an entire drawing can be inserted into a different drawing as a block. When this is used the base point will default to ________.", "opta": "0,0", "optb": "10,10", "optc": "20,20", "optd": "30,30", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When creating your own blocks it is important to avoid drawing any portion of the block in the ________ layer.", "opta": "0", "optb": "center line", "optc": "hatch", "optd": "hidden line", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Newer versions of AutoCAD utilize the ________ to make block library management very easy.", "opta": "File / find", "optb": "Design Center", "optc": "File / search", "optd": "None of the above", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When the drafter types the word BLOCK or selects the Make Block tool from the Draw tool bar the ________ will appear.", "opta": "grid", "optb": "Block Text Box", "optc": "Block Definition Dialog", "optd": "None of the above", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When creating a block the drafter needs to pay particular attention to selecting a base point because it determines the ________.", "opta": "scale", "optb": "rotation angle", "optc": "insertion point", "optd": "color", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When using versions of AutoCAD prior to Release 2006 it may be necessary to ________ a block in order to edit it.", "opta": "copy", "optb": "explode", "optc": "offset", "optd": "none of the above", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Some common blocks used by architectural drafters include ________.", "opta": "door swings", "optb": "ceiling fans", "optc": "appliances", "optd": "All of the above", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Inserting blocks into a drawing file usually requires exacting placement. The drafter should insure that ________ is turned on.", "opta": "O Snaps", "optb": "Ortho", "optc": "Grid", "optd": "Dynamic Input", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}